<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Android Books</string>
  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
  <string name="dynamicUiTitle">Creating Dynamic UI with Android Fragments</string>
  <string name="dynamicUiDescription">This book introduces readers to Fragments, the specific
    scenarios Fragments address and how to use them. The book will take the reader from the basics
    of using Fragments, through their use in creating more adaptive and dynamic user experiences.
    The book teaches readers how to capitalize on many of the built-in UI features that are
    available through Fragments such list-based navigation, tab-based navigation, and layout
    adaptation, as well as how to customize an app’s UI behavior by directly managing the creation,
    appearance, and flow of individual Fragments.
  </string>
  <string name="android4NewTitle">Android 4: New Features for Application Development</string>
  <string name="android4NewDescription">A practical and hands-on guide for developing android
    applications using new features of Android Ice Cream Sandwich (Android 4.0) with a step-by-step
    approach and clearly explained sample codes. You will learn the new APIs in Android 4.0 with
    sample code.
  </string>
  <string name="androidSysDevTitle">Instant Android Systems Development How-to</string>
  <string name="androidSysDevDescription">Provides a gentle introduction to the platform internals
    without sacrificing depth. Source code examples are designed to be meaningful, but at the same
    time, do not disguise their real purpose, which is to illustrate systems development techniques
    and common design patterns in android systems programming.
  </string>
  <string name="androidEngineTitle">AndEngine for Android Game Development Cookbook</string>
  <string name="androidEngineDescription">Contains all of the necessary information and examples in
    order to build the games as you imagine them.
  </string>
  <string name="androidDbProgTitle">Android Database Programming</string>
  <string name="androidDbProgDescription">Designed to help developers create and design data-centric
    mobile applications on Google’s Android platform. As the world goes increasingly mobile and as
    consumers’ demand for data-centric applications rises, knowing how to combine the two
    effectively will become an increasingly important asset to have as a developer. The book starts
    by looking at the various local data storage methods on Android, and finishes off by examining
    external databases and ways you can utilize them from within an Android application.
  </string>
  <string name="activityMainLabel">Android Books</string>
  <string name="bookIndexErrorMessage">Book Index Value Out Of Range</string>
  <string name="title_activity_book_desc">Book Description</string>
</resources>
